Here.Have a shufti of that.
给你 看看这个
- What are these? - That's the police logthe day that Robin got murdered.
-这些是什么  -这是罗宾遇害那天的警方日志
Couple of bar fights. A few cars got nicked.
几场酒吧斗殴  几辆车被偷了
But you know what's not in there?
但你知道里面缺了什么吗
No bank alarms going off.
没有银行警报被触发
No one charged at Central Booking.
中央拘留所里没有人被起诉
A train stopped two bank robbers, my arse.Someone's fucking hiding something.
火车头才没有阻止那两个银行劫匪妈的肯定有人在隐瞒什么东西
- Hiding what? - Well, I don't know, whatever dodgy shit he was up to that night.
-隐瞒什么  -我也不知道也许就是他那晚干了什么破事
Why couldn't he stop? I mean, what was in that bag?
为什么他不停下来  那袋子里究竟有什么东西
You know? Who was he running from?
他在躲谁
- Or where was he running to? - Bingo.
-又或者说他要跑到哪里去  -没错
Work that out, and we'll have the fucker, I can smell it.
搞清楚这个  那傻逼就完蛋了  相信我
Okay.
好吧